《谍影迷情》前情提要
Previously on "Covert Affairs"...
秘密行动处让我为你建立一个档案
The D.C.S. asked me to start a file on you.
布雷斯怀特在调查我
Braithwaite is investigating me.
海伦就像安全阀  在我们俩之间传递消息
Helen's been our cutout, passing messages between us.
一周前  我让她更深入到
I pulled her in more fully into
调查亨利的形势中去
Henry's situation about a week ago.
坎贝尔处长  很荣幸您能来
Director Campbell, it's an honor to have you.
我不再是处长了
I'm actually not a director anymore.
我找个人  叫里斯
Is one of you guys Reese?
我就住在隔壁
I'm just next door.
我帮忙收租  还帮房东修厕所
I collect the rent, fix broken toilets for the landlords,
他就给我行点方便
so he gives me a break.
我叫桑娜
I'm Sana.
我失去了我的儿子  杰
I lost my son, Jai.
杰是我的朋友  我也失去了他
Jai was my friend. I lost him too.
我认为你足够聪明  能帮我扳倒亨利
And I think you are smart enough to help me take Henry down.
安德鲁・古德曼  欢迎到来
Ah, Andrew Goodman. Bienvenue. Welcome.
亨利下令把那架直升机击落
Henry ordered that helicopter shot down,
你就是发射导弹的人
and you were the one that fired the missile.
这都算不上是一个问题
That's not even a question.
你要对戴维・都普瑞斯干什么
What are you planning on doing to David Dupres?
快说
Tell her.
说他要对戴维干什么
Tell her what he's gonna do to david!
桑娜
Sana!
瑞士  日内瓦
翻译：灰灰是菇凉   超级大汉堡
翻译：salaph   olivia_xuxu   胖兔纯
翻译：Reginamoon   米苏
校对：油炸电风扇   米苏
总监：米苏
时间轴：宝宝   大喷子   全家筒
后期：IcyLisle
为什么在这里停下
Why are we stopping here?
我想喝一杯
I could use a drink.
你呢
You?
给我来杯培恩龙舌兰
Can I have a shot of Patron?
你想喝什么
What do you want?
不要  我不想喝
Nothing. I don't want a drink.
来两杯  能记在酒店房间的帐上吗
Make it two, and can you charge it to the room?
记在住店客人古德曼账上
It's under the name Goodman.
想知道我们为什么来这吗
You want to know what we're doing here?
亨利・威尔库克斯  情况怎样
亨利每半小时发短信给安德鲁
Henry's been texting Andrew every half hour
询问进度报告
asking for a progress report.
所以呢
So?
这里是是安德鲁・古德曼的酒店
So this is Andrew Goodman's hotel.
这里是想要弄清
It's the best place to figure out
怎么回复这些短信的最佳地点
how to answer those texts.
我们留在你公寓的尸体怎么办
What about the dead body we left in your apartment?
有人会听到枪声
Somebody will have heard the gunshots.
回去找尸体的
They're going to find the body.
只是时间问题
It's only a matter of when.
那就意味着警察会搜捕我们
That means the police are gonna be after us,
现在还没的话
if they're not already,
等到他们确定尸体身份之后就会了
as soon as they I.D. it.
想确定一个没有证件的人的身份是很难的
It's hard to I.D. a body with no I.D.
我怀疑他根本不叫古德曼
I doubt his name was even Goodman.
他是专业的影子杀手
He's a professional ghost.
希望他对自己的工作很在行
I'm counting on the fact that he was good at his job.
安德鲁・古德曼至少还要
Andrew Goodman will be a John Doe
做一段时间的无名氏
at least for a little while.
但愿能给我们争取足够的时间
Hopefully, that'll give us enough time.
要足够的时间做什么
Enough time for what?
反击
Counterstrike.
亨利不知道他的人死了
Henry doesn't know his guy is dead,
这也许是前所未有的一次
so maybe for the first time ever,
我知道了他不知道的事
I know something he doesn't.
喝了
Drink up.
我们去看看安德鲁・古德曼留下了什么
We're gonna go see what Andrew Goodman left behind.
425号房
Room 425.
你真的不知道你在做什么  对吧
You really have no idea what you're doing, do you?
你闯进我的审讯室
You stormed into my interrogation
是因为你不顾一切地想弄清楚
because you were so desperate to find out
安德鲁要对戴维做什么
what Andrew was planning for David.
现在安德鲁死了
Well, Andrew is dead.
答案只能在这里了
The answers are here.
一定在这里
They have to be.
把电视开大声
Turn on the TV loud.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
再大点
Louder.
我们要睡觉了
对不起  遥控器卡住了
关掉
Turn it off.
找到了
Bingo.
我需要破译密码
I need to decrypt this password
再找个安全的地方读取硬盘信息
and find a safe place to read the drive,
那样就要很多时间
and that's gonna take time--
而你现在没有足够时间了
Time that you don't have right now.
因为戴维会想知道我去哪儿了
'Cause David's wondering where I am.
回家让他放心
Go home and put him at ease.
对他撒谎
Lie to him?
你再说一遍事情过程
Go through the story again.
我要听你说一次
I need to hear you say it.
我以前撒过谎
I have lied before.
再说一遍
Say it again.
快
Go.
你在会议后跟踪安德鲁
When you followed Andrew out of the meeting,
你担心自己会搞砸生意  心烦意乱
you were distraught you'd blown the deal.
我们在酒店喝了一杯
We grabbed a drink at a hotel.
我把你安抚好了  花的时间
I calmed you down, which took longer
比预想的要长
than either of us expected.
你明天回去工作  没有了傲气
You'll be back into work in the morning, pride bruised,
打算弥补戴维
ready to make it up to David.
很好
Good.
回家好好睡一觉
Go home and try to get some sleep.
肯定睡不着
Sleep isn't on the cards.
我们刚刚拷打了一个人
We tortured a man.
你开枪打了他  他死了
You shot him. He's dead.
你都没关系吗
It doesn't affect you?
我没时间
I don't have time.
我们没有时间
We don't have time.
你想保护戴维
You want to protect David?
我们就得赶快行动
We have to move fast,
-我需要你相信我  -相信你
- and I need you to trust me.   - Trust you?
你以为装出一副强硬的外表
You think a tough exterior is going to cover the fact
就能掩盖你不知如何对付亨利的事实吗
that you have no idea how to handle Henry?
我与他结婚11年
I was married to him for 11 years
而且在此之前还是他的线人
and his asset before that.
间谍游戏他比你在行
He's better at this than you.
回家去吧  桑娜
Go home, Sana.
亨利・威尔库克斯  状况如何
谍 影 迷 情
第四季  第十二集
■
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
你男人还在睡吗
Your man still sleeping it off?
不  不完全是
No. Not exactly.
我能...  能借一步说话吗
Can I... can we talk?
稍等
Just a second.
他死了
He's dead.
死了
Dead?
我们起了争执  愈演愈烈
We got in a fight. It got rough.
我必须得自我防卫
I had to defend myself.
听起来是那混蛋罪有应得
Sounds like it serves the asshole right.
这能让你冷静下来
This'll calm you down.
不  谢了  我不能吸
No, thanks. I can't.
我得想清楚该怎么办
I have to figure out what to do.
我摊上大事了
I'm in some serious shit,
而且没人能帮我
and I don't have anyone who's gonna help me.
你也有相似的经历  不是吗
You've been through this before, right?
你说过你继父会殴打你妈妈
You said your stepdad hit your mom?
是  是没错  我为此恨透了那混球
Yeah, yeah, and I hated the prick for it,
但我也没有把他给杀了啊
but I've never killed him.
抱歉  我不该想着...
I'm sorry. I shouldn't-I shouldn't have thought...
等等  你需要什么
Wait, wait. What do you need?
假装你不知道我在哪
Pretend like you don't know where I am,
就说我好几天都没回过那房间
like, I haven't been here for days.
假装你不知道我去哪了
You don't know where I went.
就说你不知道那男人是谁
Like, you have no idea who this guy is.
给我争取点时间
Buy me some time.
是楼宇管理员打来的
This is the building manager.
拜托  里斯
Please, Reese.
有事吗
Yeah?
等等  什么
Wait, what?
好  好  我马上回去  待会见
Okay, okay. I'll run over. I'll see you soon.
他们发现尸体了
They found the body.
你要怎么跟他们说
What are you gonna tell 'em?
你好久没回去了  几天前就走了
You weren't there. You left days ago,
我不知道你的行踪也联系不到你  行吗
and I don't know where to find you, all right?
谁
Who is it?
是我
It's me.
你想要什么  海伦
What do you want, Helen?
我得隐蔽自己的行踪
I have to be careful where I'm seen.
能让我进去吗
Can I please come in?
当影子特工是你自己的选择
It was your decision to become a ghost.
别指望我会帮你隐瞒
Don't expect me to help you keep up that lie.
我没指望过
I don't.
坎贝尔夫妇请我为亚瑟的辩护帮忙
The Campbells have asked for my help with Arthur's defense.
所以你现在的身份是律师吗
Oh, you're a lawyer now?
我知道你现在一定悲痛万分
I know you must be in a lot of pain,
对安妮的事情我深感抱歉
and I am deeply sorry about Annie,
但我需要知道在哥本哈根
but I need to know everything that happened between
她跟亨利之间发生的每一件事
her and Henry in Copenhagen
只有如此我才能证明亨利与袭击有关
if I'm gonna find any evidence to tie him to the attack
以此为亚瑟洗脱罪名
and exonerate Arthur.
好了  你我之间永远不能谈及安妮
Okay, you and I don't talk about Annie ever.
明白吗
Understand?
我能理解你现在所经历的痛苦
I understand what you must be going through.
一派胡言  你就是冲着安妮的死而来的
Bullshit. I think you're here because Annie's gone.
亚瑟和琼有让你帮忙吗
Did Arthur and Joan even ask for your help,
还是你毛遂自荐
or did you offer it
想以此将功补过
trying to clean your slate across the board?
你说得没错
You're right.
我的确有很多过错需要弥补
I have so much to make up for.
太晚了
It's too late.
我不奢望你会原谅我
I don't ever expect you to forgive me,
但你得知道我从没放弃过你妻子的身份
but I need you to know I never stopped being your wife,
这七年来一刻都没放弃过
not for one moment in seven years,
随着时间的流逝
and the longer it went on,
我越来越清楚地意识到我犯下了大错
the more I realized what a mistake I had made,
但我不能改变当初的决定
but I couldn't take it back.
你以为你现在就能改变当初的决定吗
You think you can take it back now?
-我还是你的妻子  奥吉  -真的吗
- I'm still your wife, Auggie. - Really?
因为上次你来的时候
Because the last time you were here,
说得很清楚不是这么一回事
you made it very clear that's not the case.
自从你舍弃海伦・汉森这身份
You have not been my wife
伪装成他人那一刻起
since the second you became somebody else
你就不是我的妻子了
other than Helen Hansen.
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are.
我还是一样的我
I am still the same person.
但我变了
Well, I'm not.
我亲眼看着你死去
I watched you die.
你知道我花了多长时间才走出来吗
Do you have any idea how long it took me to get over that?
到头来居然都是个弥天大谎
And it was all a lie.
我能理解
I understand,
我也希望在你的痛楚与愤恨之下
and I hope under all that hurt and anger,
你终有一日能理解我
you will too someday.
我们彼此相爱  奥吉
We loved each other, Auggie.
正如你所说  那是很久以前的事了
It was a long time ago, just like you said.
我不能改变我做过的错事
I can't change what I did,
但我能帮你们对付亨利
but I can help all of you against Henry,
让他为他所犯下的罪恶付出代价
make him pay for what he's done.
他才是真正的敌人  不是吗
He's the real enemy, isn't he?
这项链是你在罗马的时候送我的
This is the necklace you gave me in Rome.
我从没摘下来过
I never stopped wearing it.
也许是时候摘下来了
Maybe it's time you did.
我会告诉你亨利的调查结果
I'll let you know what I find out about Henry.
他们确认那具尸体的身份了吗
Have they I.D.'d the body yet?
我不知道
I don't know.
戴维还在你身边吗
Is David still with you?
他去健身房了
He went to the gym.
你在笔记本上找到什么线索了吗
Did you find anything on the laptop?
没有  笔记本加密了
No, the laptop was safeguarded...
是专业级的加密
Professional Grade.
这需要用暴力破解
It's gonna need brute-force decryption.
你能做到吗
Can you do that?
不行  但U盘里有些东西
No. But there was something on the flash drive.
-什么东西  -一些文件
- Something? - Files.
文件
Files?
告诉我  亨利的计划是什么
Tell me. What's Henry's plan?
-这些文件是干什么的  -陷害戴维
- What are the files for? - To set David up.
让他看上去跟哥本哈根的袭击有关
To make it look like he knew about the attack in Copenhagen,
像他知道内幕消息  并从中获利
like he profited from it, that he had inside knowledge.
戴维跟那事一点关系都没有
David had nothing to do with that.
我知道  但亨利想让大家这么认为
I know, but Henry wants it to look that way.
上传成功
那你准备怎么办
So what are you gonna do?
在我们通话的时候我已经在行动了
I'm working on a plan as we speak.
按计划进行
戴维・都普瑞斯
洁西卡
Jessica?
戴维  你好
David. Hi.
早上好
Good morning.
你来的真早
You're in early.
我来做一些工作
Yeah, I was just working.
我们来谈谈昨天发生的事情
Let's talk about what happened yesterday.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
桑娜是怎么说的
Um, what did Sana say?
她尝试着安抚我
She tried to calm me down.
我那时对你很生气
I was so angry at you.
但她让我明白了
But then she made me realize
昨天那件事是古德曼的责任
that what happened yesterday was Goodman's fault,
并不是你的错
not yours.
她真是我不可缺少的另一半
She's the saucer to my teacup.
她是个了不起的女人
She is a remarkable woman.
你知道吗
You know what?
我会打电话给古德曼  告诉他下不为例
I'm going to call Goodman today to read him the riot act.
我等这个新硬盘已经一个多星期了
I've been waiting over a week for a new hard drive, okay?
如果... 奥吉  抱歉哥们
If... Auggie, sorry, man.
稍等我一下
Just give me one second.
如果允许我自己买一个带进来
If I could buy one and bring it in,
-我早就会这么做了  -巴伯
- You know I would do that, okay?   - Barber.
没事  我拿到了
Never mind. I got it.
谢谢  说真的  谢谢你了
Thank you. Sincerely, thank you so much.
交几个底层的朋友还是有好处的
It's good to have friends in low places.
他们现在就让你做这个吗
Oh, man, is this what they have you doing now?
那倒不是  特地为你拿上来的
No, it's a special delivery.
你昨晚去哪了
Where were you last night?
我以为你终于决定去阿伦酒馆转转了
I thought you were gonna finally come out to Allen's, man.
你好久都没有好好放松一下了
It's been way too long since you came out.
我有些别的事情
Yeah, I--I got caught up.
你知道这些背景调查的原因吗
Hey, what's with all these background checks?
最近把大家都弄得疑神疑鬼的
There is an increasingly thick cloud of paranoia going around.
还以为只有我这么觉得呢
You know, I thought it was just me.
不只是你
It's not.
他们增添了新服务器来储存额外数据
They're adding servers to hold extra data,
我还听说布雷斯怀特正在暗中
And I heard Braithwaite opened a blue file
调查亨利・威尔库克斯
on Henry Wilcox.
真的  好吧
Really? Huh.
我还以为布雷斯怀特听命于威尔库克斯
I thought Wilcox had Braithwaite in his pocket.
我也这么以为的
I did too.
这事别跟别人说  行吗
Hey, keep that one under your hat, all right?
放心  不会乱说的  哥们
Yeah, it's under the hat, man.
一定守口如瓶
It's under the hat.
汤米  汤米
Hey, Tommy. Tommy.
我们的流言计划进行得如何
How'd it go with patient zero?
很快就会传到亨利和布雷斯怀特的耳里了
One wedge between Henry and Braithwaite coming up.
至今我都不明白为什么一屋子的间谍们
It still amazes me how bad a building full of spies
却守不住秘密
is at keeping a secret.
什么时候能知道这个起作用了
When will we know this is working?
但亨利找你谈话而不找布雷斯怀特的时候
When Henry wants to talk to you instead of Braithwaite.
-他有什么情况通知我  -明白
- Let me know when he reaches out. - Yeah.
有什么可以帮到你们吗
Can I help you?
我们是来找戴维・都普瑞斯的
We are here to see David Dupres.
跟我来  这边请
Come with me. Right this way.
他们是什么人
Who are those people?
说是国际刑警
They said they're with Interpol.
不可能  我从没见过那些文件
不好意思  你得跟我们走一趟
别碰我  我自己会走
-戴维  -是国际刑警
- David? - Interpol.
他们要带我回办事处
They're bringing me down to their offices
询问一些有关我电脑里文件的问题
for questioning about some files on my computer.
关于什么
About what?
他们怀疑我跟哥本哈根
They think I had something to do
那架直升机坠落事件有关
with the helicopter going down in Copenhagen.
这只是个误会
It's just a misunderstanding.
打给柯林的律所
Call Colin's firm.
让他去国际刑警办事处找我
Tell him to meet me at the interpol office.
好的
Of course.
大家都回去工作吧
Everybody, back to work.
不会有事的
It'll be fine.
洁西卡
Jessica...
Jessica.
你说的一切都发生了
Everything you said happened.
他们对戴维出手了
They came after David.
亨利是怎么做到的
How did Henry do it?
他是怎么把文件放进戴维的电脑里的
How did he get the files on David's computer?
不是亨利干的
Henry didn't do it.
是我
I did.
是我今早放进去的
I loaded the files this morning.
你让国际刑警抓走了我的未婚夫
You had Interpol drag my fiance away?
不  是亨利联系的国际刑警
No. Henry must have called Interpol.
这是他计划中的下一步
It's the next logical phase in his plan.
一旦亨利发现安德鲁・古德曼已经死了
Sana, as soon as Henry realizes Andrew Goodman is dead,
我们就什么都做不了了  桑娜
there is nothing else we can do.
安德鲁本该为他把文件放进戴维电脑的
He expected Andrew to plant that intel,
所以我这么做了
So I did it.
虽然有一定的风险
It's a calculated risk,
但只要真相一大白  戴维就会没事的
but David will be fine as soon as the real truth emerges.
你说过你在制定计划的
You said you were working on a plan.
我想我们在你行动之前最好讨论讨论
I figured we'd discuss it before you acted.
你说过你不想向戴维撒谎
You said you had a hard time lying to David,
所以我避免了让你再次那么做
so I prevented you from having to do that again.
多么崇高啊
How lofty.
所以你这么做是为了我
So you did this for me?
我在试图证明
I am trying to prove
亨利才是哥本哈根袭击案的幕后黑手
that Henry is the architect of the Copenhagen attacks.
我们在"跟着钱走"
We are following the money.
找出亨利是如何转移现金的
finding out how Henry moves his cash
是还戴维自由之身的第一步
is the first step into getting David free,
而我有办法能让我们做成这件事
and I have a way we can do that.
在这之前戴维一直都是自由之身
David was already free.
亨利是你儿子死亡的原因
Henry is the reason your son is dead.
解释你刚刚说的话
Explain that.
炸弹爆炸时我在场
I was there when the bomb went off.
杰和我在一个小餐馆见面
Jai and I had met at a diner.
我本应和他一起上车的
I was supposed to be in the car with him,
但是我忘了拿我的雨伞
but I forgot my umbrella.
就在那时炸弹爆炸了
That's when it happened.
是亨利做的
And Henry did this?
他告诉了你什么
What did he tell you?
他说这是亚瑟・坎贝尔的错
He said it was Arthur Campbell's fault,
还说很快全世界就会知道真相了
that soon the world would know the truth.
而且他很生气
And he was angry.
那不是生气
It wasn't anger.
而是愧疚
It was guilt.
那个放炸弹的男人是一位前特工
The man who set the bomb was a former operative
而亨利背弃了他
that Henry had turned his back on.
亨利将他对杰的死亡的愧疚
Henry has been projecting his guilt about Jai's death
投射到他身边的所有人身上
onto everyone around him...
摧毁生命
Destroying lives.
除非有人阻止他  不然他是不会停下的
He is not gonna stop until someone stops him.
让我们一起阻止他吧
Let's stop him.
你想要我做什么
What do you want me to do?
我们得找个私密点的地方
We're gonna need somewhere more private.
楼上有个空的办公间
There's an empty office space upstairs.
托马斯・欣克利雪茄
政治就是场滑稽的游戏
Politics are a funny game.
假如我们之前对菲德尔能有一点不同的话
Perhaps if we'd treated Fidel a bit differently,
我们就可以买到好东西了
we could be shopping for the good stuff.
亨利  我  我不知道你抽雪茄
Henry, I--I didn't know you were a cigar man.
我有诸多恶习
I have many vices.
为什么我听说你在秘密调查我
What's this I hear about you opening a blue file on me?
你从哪听来的
Where'd you hear that?
-所以说是真的了  -不  不是的
- So it's true? - Not, it's not.
就是  没有
It's--no.
听着  不管是谁告诉你的  这都是个误会
Look, whoever told you that is mistaken.
如果你想要卡斯特罗抽的那种
If you want what Castro smokes,
去后面的屋子找阿图罗
talk to Arturo in the back room.
告诉他是我让你来的
Tell him I sent you.
但说实话  我觉得它们对你而言太强劲了
But honestly, I think they're too strong for you.
你好  桑娜
Hello, Sana.
真是惊喜啊
What a surprise.
听到你的声音真是太好了
So good to hear from you.
希望我没有打扰到你
I hope I haven't caught you at a bad time.
是你打来的话什么时候都不会打扰我
It's always a good time to hear your voice,
虽然  我从你的声音中听出了点什么
though, I'm hearing something in it.
一切都还好吗
Is everything all right?
我一直在想你在法兰克福说的东西
I've been thinking about what you said in Frankfurt--
你说的关于戴维的事
What you said about David.
他做了什么
What did he do?
他现在有麻烦了
He's in trouble.
亨利  我真的不想在电话里和你谈论这个
Henry, I'd really rather not do this on the phone.
你能来日内瓦吗
Can you come to Geneva?
当然
Of course.
我可以搭下一班飞机过来
I can get on the next plane out.
谢谢你  亨利
Thank you, Henry.
我在法兰克福说的话是认真的
I meant what I said in Frankfurt.
我愿意为你做任何事
I'd do anything for you.
到时见
See you soon.
所以他在赶来日内瓦了
So he's coming to geneva.
现在怎么办
What now?
我们会再聚一次
We'll reconvene
在你和亨利坐下来谈谈之前的早上
in the morning before you sit down with Henry.
然后我还要做我曾发誓永远不做的事
And do the thing I vowed I'd never do again.
他为了你来日内瓦
He's coming to Geneva for you.
你掌控着全局
You're in control.
我的未婚夫被拘留了
My fiance's in custody,
而我在听你命令行事
and I'm taking orders from you.
原谅我一点都不觉得我掌控着全局
Forgive me for not feeling in control.
奥吉
Auggie.
琼
Joan.
你下IT部来做什么
What are you doing down here in I.T.?
我
I...
我看到你和考尔德讲话了
I saw you talking to Calder.
是啊  我们为同一个组织工作呢
Yeah, we work for the same agency.
这是无法避免的
It couldn't be helped.
发生什么了
What's going on?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我的意思是  考尔德杀了安妮
I mean, Calder killed Annie.
我很震惊你甚至还和他打招呼
I'm stunned you'd even be acknowledging him.
现在  假如你告诉我你在监视他
Now, if you tell me you've been keeping tabs on him
或者调查他  我能理解
or investigating him, I would understand.
我不能谈论这件事
I can't talk about it.
不能还是不想
Can't or won't?
既不能  也不想
I can't. I won't.
这不像你
This isn't like you.
你又在干什么呢
What about you?
我怎么了
What about me?
你和亚瑟雇了海伦
You and Arthur hired Helen.
是的  她跟着亨利去了日内瓦
Yes. She's following Henry to Geneva.
她去了日内瓦
She's going to geneva?
我们想着她说不定能
We thought she might be able
弄清楚亨利的经济状况
to shed some light on Henry's finances.
奥吉  我在一个小房子里工作  做着文案工作
Auggie, I am working in a box, pushing papers.
而你在这下面
You're down here.
我俩都失去了太多
We have both lost so much.
我不会为尽我权力范围内一切能力为我丈夫辩护
I'm not gonna apologize for doing everything in my power
而道歉
to defend my husband.
我没有要你道歉
I'm not asking you to apologize.
现在只剩你我二人了
It is just you and me.
我们是仅存的希望
We're all that's left.
我们两个都要记住这一点
We both need to remember that.
你什么时候见亨利
When are you seeing Henry?
半小时后  在日内瓦咖啡馆
Half an hour. Cafe Geneve.
在他住的多希尔酒店附近
It's near the hotel Dorciere where he's staying.
你45分钟后再去
45 minutes.
让他等着
Let's make him wait.
亨利不喜欢等人
Henry hates waiting.
正因如此
Exactly.
你以为这能让他放下戒备
You may think that'll soften him up,
但这么做并不英明
but it's not the right move.
是我打过去的
That's me calling.
接起来  然后不要挂断
Answer it and leave the connection open.
这样我就能听到你们的对话
Then I can listen during the meet.
来试一下
Let's test it.
亨利不喜欢等人
Henry hates waiting.
就是要让他等得着急
We want him on the tilt.
你坐下后  说他想听到的话
When you sit down, tell him everything he wants to hear--
说你很担心戴维
That you're worried about David.
你很痛苦
You're in distress.
这些都是事实
You mean the truth.
你只需要和他谈一小会儿
You only have to talk to him for a little while.
之后我会给亨利设一个陷阱
Then I'm gonna throw a wrench into Henry's world,
然后你就可以离开了
and you can leave right after that.
你要去哪里
Where are you gonna be?
我要去办一些相关的事情
I have some related things I need to take care of.
我还是亨利的妻子时
When I was Henry's asset,
我们见面时他从不让我
he wouldn't let me out of his sight
离开他的视线
when there was a meet.
人们管那叫做"迷恋"
They call that infatuation.
我认为那是因为他擅长操控别人
I call that being a great handler.
那个男人曾经包容又可靠
The man was inclusive and reassuring--
这些特质你都没有
everything you're not.
他会和我反复演练一个场景
We'd go over a scenario
直到我感觉安全
until he knew I felt safe.
他有那么多时间
He had the luxury of time
还有中情局在背后支持他
and the full backing of the CIA.
我们没有那些资源
We don't have that.
我不再有那些资源了
I don't have that anymore.
这是最好的计划  桑娜
This is the best plan, Sana.
你必须信任我
You need to trust me.
我们可以不要再用"信任"这个词了吗
Can we agree not to use that word again?
现在谈信任已经太晚了
It's much too late for trust.
桑娜
Sana.
抱歉我迟到了
I'm sorry I'm late.
没事的
That's quite all right.
咖啡馆里在播放德彪西的歌曲呢
They were just playing some Debussy in the cafe here.
《月光曲》吗
Clair De Lune?
是的  我想这是个预兆
Yes. I figured it was a sign.
或者是你计划好的
Or you planned it.
不是  如果是我计划好的
Nah, if I'd have planned it,
歌曲应该还在继续
they'd still be playing.
请坐
Sit down.
别担心
Don't you worried.
听我说  桑娜
Listen to me, Sana.
我已经找人去查了戴维的背景
I already have men looking into David.
你有没有预料到会发生这些事
Did you see any of this happening?
我们在法兰克福见面后  你有没有查他
Did you look into him after what I told you in Frankfurt?
没有  我应该查一查的
No, I should have.
戴维一直是个很重视隐私的人
David's always been very private.
我可以帮你
I can help you.
还可以帮戴维
I can help David.
-我可以保护你的安全  -安全
- I can keep you safe. - Safe...
跟我说说发生了什么
Tell me everything that's happened,
有没有什么不寻常的事情
Anything out of the ordinary.
不寻常
Out of the ordinary?
戴维的行为
David's behavior?
办公室有没有出现新面孔
Um, new visitors to the office?
奇怪的来往
Strange interactions?
没有  我不知道
No, I--I don't know. It's--
告诉我  桑娜
Tell me, Sana.
我需要知道所有事
I need to know everything.
整件事都很奇怪
It's this whole situation.
我就是不敢相信
I just can't believe David
戴维会牵扯到这种事里面
would be involved in something like this.
我会帮你度过这个难关
I'll help get you through this.
我会是你的坚强后盾
I will always help you.
我一直在想杰  还有我们两个的事
I've been thinking about Jai, thinking about us.
试着重拾自己的生活
Trying to get my life back.
你要回局里吗
Going back to the agency?
我的新公司比中情局强得多
My new company is doing the agency one better.
等尘埃落定  莱克星顿会让中情局
When all is said and done, Lexington will make the CIA
看起来比现在还要跟不上形势
look even more out of touch than it already is.
抱歉
Excuse me.
这么说吧
Put this away,
发自: 安・古德曼
午餐结束  快回酒店
没什么事吧
Everything okay?
没事
Fine.
如果你有事要处理
If you have something to take care of,
我们可以改天再见
we can meet later.
不  没事
No, no--
发自: 安・古德曼
立即回来
-我还是走吧  -桑娜
- I should get going. - Sana--
没事的  没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
我们再聊
Let's speak soon.
好的
Yes.
谢谢你  亨利
Thank you, Henry.
不用客气
You're welcome.
发自: 亨利
你最好是有重要的事
回到酒店了
发自: 安・古德曼
很好  现在谈谈钱的事
我需要三百万
他还爱着你
He's still in love with you.
他想要你回到他身边
He wants you back.
我能从他的声音里听出来
I heard it in his voice,
他会不惜一切来达到这个目的
and he will do anything to make that happen,
包括买通安德鲁
including paying off Andrew.
安德鲁・古德曼
三小时内给我三百万美元
否则我会告诉桑娜所有事情
他一旦汇款  我们就能跟踪资金流向
Once he wires the money, we can track the flow
找到他的同伙
and find out who he's working with,
并能把他和我们红头发的朋友联系起来
and it links him to our red-haired friend.
这样做很投机
This feels speculative.
这只是冰山一角
It's just breadcrumbs.
如果发挥作用就不是冰山一角了
It's always just breadcrumbs until it becomes something more.
你懂得
You know that.
是亨利
Henry.
我们要激怒他
We're getting a rise out of him.
你到底想干什么
So what the hell are you doing?
你要明白你只是一颗棋子
You realize I--I put you into this game we play,
我可以把你弃掉
and I can pluck you out.
你不想让维尔莉特
I'm sure you wouldn't want anything
出什么事吧
to happen to Violet, would you?
你知道维尔莉特是谁吗
Do you know who Violet is?
不知道
No.
安德鲁・古德曼
看看地图集下面
真不希望桑娜看到
哥本哈根地图
我需要六个小时
他上钩了
We've got him.
只有三个小时
会成功的  桑娜
This is gonna work, Sana.
时间不多了
Clock's ticking.
接收帐户都准备好了吗
Is the receiving account all set?
我通过瑞士金融市场监督管理局
I fabricated a dummy account for Goodman
为古德曼伪造了一个虚拟账户
through FINMA,
并加上了必要的电子标签
put the necessary e-tags on it.
他一旦汇款
Once he transfers the money,
我们就能找到资金来源
we can locate the origin electronically.
冰山一角
Your breadcrumb.
对
Yeah.
做这么多都只是为了冰山一角
All this for a breadcrumb.
怎样才能得到一切呢
What's it gonna take to get the whole bakery?
纳尔逊  是我
Nelson, this is me.
我有点麻烦事
I'm--I'm in a bit of a bind.
你竟然直接给我打电话
You're calling me directly?
我需要不能被追踪的三百万美元
I need $3 million, untraceable,
越快越好
fast-tracked.
好的  没问题
Okay, all right.
要多快
Define "Fast-track."
三小时内
Three hours.
你在哪里
Where are you?
日内瓦
Geneva.
你怎么会在日内...
You're in Gen--
我不能穿越时空...
Look, I can't bend the laws of space and time--
我跟你做了这么多生意你就不能帮我
I've done enough business with you to warrant
这个忙吗
this favor.
我会尽力的
I'll do my best.
多谢你了  尼尔森
Thank you, Nelson.
我们不能再在楼里见面了
All right, no more meeting inside the building.
我们还得像这样见面
We have to continue to talk like this.
好吧
Yeah.
今天亨利从办公室来电
Henry's office called me today.
他想在回来后两天内找我谈谈
He wants to sit down in two days when he's back in town...
布雷思韦特不在场
without Braithwaite.
亨利在日内瓦
Henry's in Geneva.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
这很复杂
It's complicated.
说实话
That's not an answer.
你联系过安妮了
Are you in touch with Annie?
当然没有
Absolutely not.
但你想现在就和她联系是不是
but you want to reach out now, don't you?
当然不是
Absolutely not.
那样会让她有危险
That'd put her at risk.
安妮这次必须独自完成这个任务
Annie's gonna have to live through this mission by herself.
你最好牢记这点
You remember that.
怎么了
Yeah?
我找到一个人能满足你的需要
I found somebody who can accommodate your needs.
我需要知道把资金转到哪里
I just need to know where to send the funds.
很好
Excellent.
我马上把收款账户发给你
I'll email you the receivable account details shortly.
有什么消息吗
What do you got for me?
我找到了你想找的人
I found what you were looking for.
敲诈我的那个人在哪儿
Where's my blackmailing friend?
他死了
He's dead.
他们在明山街的停尸房中找到了他
They have him at the morgue at the rue de Mont Brillant.
他最早被发现于一个女人的公寓中
He was found in a woman's apartment.
我们仍在调查
We're checking it out.
他死了多长时间了
How long has he been dead?
很难说准
Hard to say exactly.
不过他们找到他至少有一天了
They've had him at least one day, though.
四点了
It's 4 o'clock.
亨利没有时间了
Henry's out of time.
汇款到了吗
Did the money transfer go through?
没有
No.
就是说这没有成功
Then it didn't work.
亨利是很守时的
Henry's always on time.
我告诉过你
I told you that.
现在怎么办
What happens now?
戴维怎么办
What happens to David?
你好
Hello?
洁西  我们需要马上谈谈
Jess, we need to talk right away.
出事了
There's a problem.
不管你是谁  我都会找到你
有我的吗
One of those for me?
为你肚子里的宝宝准备的脱因咖啡
Decaf for the baby coffee-drinker in you.
谢谢
Thank you.
办公室不错
Nice office.
你左边有个椅子
There's a chair to your left.
我一直在想
You know, I've been thinking.
你是对的
you were right.
在局里我们是一伙的所以应当分享情报
We are it in this building, and we should share intel.
所以你想打听海伦发现了些什么
so you want to know if Helen found anything?
我的确想知道
Oh, the thought had crossed my mind.
我还以为这咖啡是一份谢罪礼
I thought this was a peace offering,
原来是贿赂啊
but it's a bribe.
那是一杯拿铁
It's a latte.
我还没有收到海伦的消息
I haven't heard from Helen.
她应该现在就回来了的
I expected her back by now,
但到现在她还没有跟我联系
but she hasn't reached out.
现在该你了
Now you.
我什么
Me what?
最好给我点消息
Better give me some intel,
否则我会觉得你有所保留
or I'm gonna think you're withholding.
我听说布莱斯怀特和亨利不和
I hear Braithwaite's on the outs with Henry.
真有意思
That's interesting.
这和这栋楼里
That syncs up with the rumor
最近流传的传闻很同步
that's been going around the building
说布莱斯怀特对亨利进行调查
that Braithwaite opened an investigation into Henry,
调查他出狱后的公司
his company, and all of his holdings
以及所有财产
since he left prison.
这和你无关  是吗
You didn't have anything to do with that, did you?
你知道谁会欣赏你做了这样的举动吗
You know who would have appreciated a move like that?
安妮
Annie.
任何一名好特工都会对此欣赏这样的举动
Any good spy would have appreciated a move like that.
是啊  但是我们在为安妮哀悼
Yeah, but it's Annie we're mourning,
我还是想知道你为什么和考尔德交谈
and I still want to know why you were talking to Calder.
桑娜
Sana?
你和亨利的又一点不同
Another difference between you and Henry--
他会给我电话让我放心
He'd give me reassuring phone calls.
-而你只是把我留在那里等候  -我妥协
- You just leave me to wait-- - I'm compromised.
我得离开日内瓦
I have to leave Geneva.
我们得为下一步举动定好方案
We need to set up protocols for what to do next.
不  戴维的保释听证就在明天
No, David's bond hearing is set for tomorrow.
我会给你几部一次性手机
I will get you some burner phones--
你好  桑娜
Hello, Sana.
我一直在找你
I've been looking for you.
这里不错啊
Nice space.
你秘书说这几天你经常
Your secretary said you've been coming up here a lot
到这上面来
the past few days.
这上面还有谁陪你吗
Anyone else up here with you?
没有  只有我
No, it's just me.
你有戴维的消息吗
Have you heard anything about David?
你能想办法跟你的国际刑警朋友打个招呼吗
Were you able to speak to any of your friends at Interpol?
他们在努力解决
They're working on it.
很快我就能给你更可靠的答复了
I'll have more concrete answers for you soon.
我还是不明白到底发什么什么
I still don't understand what happened.
桑娜  我不是有意要让这听起来很冷漠  但
Sana, I don't mean this to sound cold, but...
怎么了
What is it?
你是不是完全忽略了他可能有罪的
Have you completely discounted the possibility
可能性
that he may be guilty?
我们都不了解自以为了解的人
We never know people as well as we think we do...
甚至是那些我们爱的人
Even those we love.
为什么我感觉我们说的已经不是戴维了
Why do I feel like we're not talking about David anymore?
昨天有一个短暂的瞬间
There was a brief moment yesterday
我们之间的感觉都很对
where things felt right between us,
和以往一样坐在一起吃午餐
sitting together at lunch like old times.
就在属于我们的歌开始播放时
Right after our song had just played,
我再一次  对我们心怀希望
I had hope for us again.
你的眼里闪烁着光芒
There was a sparkle in your eyes,
但那不是爱
but that sparkle wasn't love.
是背叛
It was betrayal.
你背叛了我
You betrayed me.
你吓到我了  亨利
You're scaring me, Henry.
你现在混淆不清了  不知道该信任谁
You're all mixed up, not sure who to trust.
似乎这个
Seems this...
洁西卡・马修斯是个坏影响
Jessica Matthews has been a bad influence.
她把你牵扯进来
She pulled you in,
说服你帮助她一起敲诈我
convinced you to help her blackmail me.
她在哪  桑娜
Where is she, Sana?
我不知道
I don't know.
我会找到她的
I'll find her.
你知道我会的
You know I will.
当局在找一个与安德鲁・古德曼的死
The Authorities are looking for an Indian woman
有关的印度女人
in connection with the death of Andrew Goodman.
有人见过你在那个公寓里
Someone saw you in that apartment.
这是威胁还是敲诈
Is that a threat or more blackmail?
你只有两个选择
There are only two options with you.
你太了解我了
You know me that well.
好吧  是威胁
Fine. It's a threat.
戴维永远别想拜托国际刑警
David will never get out of this mess with Interpol.
我会确保
I'll see to that.
我爱过你  桑娜  全心全意
I loved you, Sana, with all my heart.
我所做的一切都是为了你和杰
Everything I've done has been for you and Jai.
不要用我们来做你邪恶行径的借口
Don't use us as a way to justify your evil deeds.
你是和禽兽  亨利
You're a monster, Henry.
承认吧
Own it.
好吧
Fine.
我会找到洁西卡・马修斯  并杀了她
I'm going to find Jessica Matthews and kill her.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你听到他说的话了吧
Did you hear him?
他要杀了你
He's gonna kill you.
快走吧
Leave now.
你和戴维还有一个脱身的办法
There's still a way out of this for you and David.
不要装得好像你在乎我们
Don't act like you care about us.
每一步你都在利用我们
You used us every step of the way.
你就像亨利一样  让一切变得艰难
You scorched the earth, just like Henry.
桑娜  我很抱歉发生了这一切
Sana, I'm sorry about all of this,
但是我们不能停止反抗
but we can't stop fighting.
我们还有古德曼的电脑
We still have Goodman's computer.
我们还有行动要做
We still have moves to make.
我们
We?
我一直看到的都是你  你的行动
All I've seen is you, your agenda.
你似乎是一个不在乎其他任何人的人
You don't seem to be a person that cares about anyone else.
你错了
You're wrong.
我在乎我为之奋斗的每一个人
I care about everyone I am fighting for,
包括你
including you.
我们到此为止
We are done.
要打败亨利  你必须变成他
To beat Henry, you have to become him,
也许你就是
and perhaps you have.
你是个残忍的人  洁西卡
You're a monster too, Jessica.
-桑娜  -别说了  走吧
- Sana-- - No, get out of here.
立刻
Now.